pointclicktrack.com 2019-05-08

# PointClickTrack - CPA Affiliate Network - BBB Accredited - Privacy Policy

This privacy statement discloses the privacy practices for PointClickTrack ("www.PointClickTrack.com"). Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our home page. PointClickTrack respects your privacy. Our purpose in collecting information from you is to help us provide you with better service.

**Information Collection and Use**

PointClickTrack is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in any way. PointClickTrack collects information from our users at several different points on our web site.

##### PERSONAL INFORMATION

Users may visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personal information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities and our being able to provide certain services to users and to interact with users, such as in an affiliate or advertiser relationship with us. For visitors to the Site who do not share any information with us, we collect only the domain name and IP address, but not the e-mail address of such visitors to our Site.

##### AFFILIATES AND ADVERTISERS

We may collect personal information when you (i) register on the Site, (ii) fill out forms or fields on the Site, (iii) complete an application for a product or service available through the Site; and (iv) communicate with us by email, mail, text, telephone, facsimile or other electronic means. Personal information in this context may include: your name, email address, postal address, phone number, Messenger ID, social media account details, IP address, tax ID/social security number, and banking/financial information.

We may also collect non-personal identification information about users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about users’ means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system, the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information, your mobile device type, your device’s unique identifier and your mobile network information.

##### OTHER USERS

For other users of the Site (non-affiliates and non-advertisers), we collect information such as IP addresses and information regarding your browser name, the type of computer and technical information about users’ means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system, the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information, your mobile device type, your device’s unique identifier and your mobile network information.

We collect personal information if you provide information such as your name, e-mail or telephone number in the context of making an inquiry through our Site.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. For example, by setting a cookie on our site, the user would not have to input a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site. The only drawback to this is that the user will be limited in some areas of our site. We also use cookies to allow user customization on various areas of our site. Cookies are required in order to participate in our advertiser offers for proper lead reporting.

**Email**

We use the return name and email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses and names are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

**Site and Service Updates**

We also send the user site and service announcement updates. Customers are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service.

**Outbound Links to Other Web Sites**

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information.

**Our Commitment To Data Security**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**Children's Online Privacy Protection Act**

The Site is not intended for use by children and anyone who provides a date of birth under the age of 18 will be prohibited from accessing the Site. PointClickTrack.com encourages parents and guardians to be familiar with the web sites that their children visit. The Federal Trade Commission ("FTC") regulates the means by which web site operators collect and use personal information from children under 13, pursuant to the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (the "Act"). For more information about the Act and children's on-line privacy in general, visit the FTC's web site at http://www.ftc.gov.

**Frauding / Scamming**

If it is determined that you are scamming people and/or frauding offers, certain information about you, and/or your history, will be shared with other site owners/operators in our on-going community efforts to combat scamming/fraud.

**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Home page so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information**

You can access most of your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by writing to us via email ( Customer Support ) or by accessing your profile through the account page.

**How To Contact Us**

If you feel we are not abiding by this policy or should you have other questions or concerns about this privacy policy or our other policies then please contact Customer Support. 

PointClickTrack.com is ran and operated by PointClick, LLC.

**YOUR ACCEPTANCE OF THESE TERMS**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this Policy. If you do not agree to this Policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this Policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**EFFECTIVE DATE: May 25th, 2018**
